the united states
the current masters
champion
tiger
woods
would have seen this morning on the tenth hole
it was fabulous
the adoring crowd jacked up to see tiger
compete in japan for the first time
since two thousand and six every step
he's taken at a cordia
golf
narchino country club
fans have cheered cameras have clicked
here's how his day began
steve sands please to be alongside trenton now below the tiger was looking left it
took one extra bounce steve
and it found the water down the left side
so not the start he or any of those adoring thousands of people wanted
yeah
this dramatically fit of steve
just over a hundred yards
uphill and
an outshot sseto
get away with a four
and here is the paputt
always left quick bogey boogie
his second haul of the day now to avoid three straight bogeys
yeah
this was return part
so it's a three putt bogey and three first birdie of the day
came at the fourteenth up the hill tiger factor two over par going now
here's his second at fifteen from the
right rough
this is just such a good shot premiere
iplayer
i mean toss is this one right up in the air
these greens are small
great shot
maybe start to develop some momentum
yeah
this is absolute money
there two
and a then at sixteen
he began with three bogeys
how about three birdies at fourteen fifteen and sixteen in tiger
woods climball
the way back to even pull at the eighteen
this is an eagle tribe after a beautiful
second at the par five from two hundred and thirty seven yards tiger
the energy here is powerful
this first all just a short position
hole par
four
like this one
and as we go back down to tiger at the
first is ten pole of the day
craig right in the middle of the fairway
yeah
seventeen yman does he have some great
that's exactly
what he's done
good
looking shot
right here
a little bit
dark trims have settled in for tiger from now tiger
he's birdied four of his
last six holes to get it back to one under par
he is trying to get it to two an old golf
course
steve built back in nineteen sixty five
so a lot of greens slope from back to front
you could above the hole
just with matsuyama that quick
here is that power button for the tiger
that's a one hundred four after that difficult start tigers
only two shots back and hold tiger woods craig with an iron
yeah
you have some options here filled with that club
and take the left bunker out of play
it's about two fifty five
is helpful here
pitches between a couple of trees
but down the center
gonna love that one ray pitches are really narrow some players
might take it over those trees with three three yards
left whole location
maybe trying to get a little drain here phil
beautiful shot tiger putting on the display here after that terrible start
his fifth birdie in his last seven holes
that was gonna turn a little left it
didn't do it at this point
stance is gonna fly this one
i booked the
the best of the three
that tiger all of a sudden
just one shot
down t shot here for tiger street down uh five
hundred yard par four
and you take it over the tree
there is water all down the
this is a helpful breeze out of the right
this is the tree that craig's talking about
even a little bit left of it
it's downwind
but if you push it right
you get blocked out by trees
looking a little right and go through the fairway into the rough
oh that is ideal
yeah
well
in japan
most courses
do have two greens on each hole
different seasons
they played different greens one of the best iron players in the history of the game
and he's like in this one
on a good line
fantastic shot another
great verdict chance a new puddle
a couple of days ago
the trusty one in the bag
and that's the reason why birdie number six and best moves at the top of the leaderboard
after three straight bogeys
very good shot fake name in the middle of the green
and that's where he wants it
that's where he is very very intense
mentally
but yet there is that that calmness that relaxed feeling about the way
his body seems to work
got a great
really rolling the powder
well
got a great
look here
expect this to be pretty close
good looks good seventh birdie in the left ten holds the tiger woods
he doesn't like it
goes into the left ruff
it's called pj two
rules
tab ruabout two
and a half inches
and they are not mulling it
fancy
follow through
just drill it down
yeah
it's a beautiful shot just scurrying down the fair
it's really
well
advanced was that one
maybe to protect his body
follow for that range shot at this par five six for tiger
ninety one yards here for tigers
just cannot miss it left a significant fall off is looded in low
another birdie chance coming up
no
if you missed cotton
the burning test would have been his eighth birdie on the last twelve holes
there are hands on the clock
you're an extremely tommy fell left
once it
did come towards the hole
this t shirt starts with middle trying to cut
bill made run out of
controlled wing
brilliant hands will work on this shot
this is actually jumped up a little bit
coming out of the rough
strike was obviously
not as best
phil nine weeks
the way
i'm surprised
how how shis around the earnings
you talked about flipping
the switch on fourteen at the three straight bogies
it's it's amazing
how the best players in the world
have to make adjustments
that's true
but we said it in the pre game
yesterday
steve one of the things
the last few years
sure but more
on the head
and it's well down the right side
oh it's a great kick
it's not the best of lies
ninety four yards
addon
just be careful
he doesn't sort of get a jumper out of here
and go along away
the wind is helpful
center center of the green
maybe two five feet right to the flag
i think would be ideal often
there's a slightly different routine for a troubleshot
once
it gets set
it's one look
one contact is good
but it looks to me like
it's left to the flag
his best opening round in the first round of any pga tour season for tiger
investing is sixty six and twenty seven at tory pines
here guys to get it in the fairway
because frank mentioned it as preferred lies
three woodford tiger
starting down the right trying to draw
next slide to from japan
one hundred
and thirty two yards for tiger
really working on changing
its trajectory on the range
this one
the low dra working towards the flag
oh yeah
how about that nice
start
in late
so the one is back to the right
played a straight
okay
this is the nine steve
he recorded
check that one off here
yeah
it looks pretty
solid there
did it got up to his front side
really well
good posture
oh i sat down to that level
and then make their way to the pga tour
and we get to know them
so well
watching them in tournaments
like the east lake cup
there's tiger's second
taking the chance
really if you will to find something that works for them
maybe is a little outside the box
tiger now for par
right breaking pots
he hardly had any
right to left that was right to left
better angle to that or location
there's also a nine iron to tiger flights
these a little lower
you can shape it
however he chooses
best yeah
it was a slight
pull left of the flag
run out
with the low t table
and that's where it started in kel
ideal had a good tee shot here on thursday
would sit ideally to elect a white wind
it starts in the center
and let's just wind just holding it up here
just fell away to the
right at the end
but the pace was brilliant
many spectators not as many distractions
it sort of feels like a casual practice round
but in the back of your mind
you know this round counts absolutely
you see a little bit of a cut shot here
flight down starting left
and and actually hooking
that's the dreaded double cross
right
there settles down in the rough
why some of the best hands
the world of golf
really
but it's a challenging one
pretty good
right
there about five or six feet left for his par
so it was a right to left
miss earlier at the second
see
how it handles this one
oh well
done
yeah
it's about there
and i'm going on the corner
this is trying to cut it to me with it being down
when he'd run out of real estate it takes a big bounce too into the trees
frank
i think to advance it at one hundred
and twenty yards would be magnificent choke
right down
and hopefully not run through the fairway
still fine
you don't really towards the center of the green
like little hop
step there added a bit more juice to that
much less loft here
pitching back up the slope
a lot of green that he can use
and we checked a little quicker than he would have liked
and we'll have another freedom
not quite at that
sort of level
right now
but this is another big party
so you make a six on a par five
right that one in think he
i'm much flatter
and pulled and not try to cut
so kate
he's not as sharp with his irons today
thought they
and he's a couple back
look at that
he is very comfortable with left to right pots
this week and welcome back tiger woods on the team of the fairway wood
and just threw three wood on the ground
this whole plan
straight down winded
cutting down the right hand side here phil
he came out of that one a little bit
and we'll miss the fairway to the right bunker and the flagstick
so launched way up in there
and has found that front bunker fill
a little more short game
magic
every commercial break
you would have seen tiger's bunker shot this one here
played it very well
got such great hands
suddenly he fell
but the lie was very gogy
because there are no people out here
there's no question
he's focused
but maybe not the intensity and gaining that in
breeze has freshened here
and back into his face that going left
rattles around the tree
oh how about that so unlike
what happened at six
when it just went through the trees
info tiger back into the wind
he chases that one up onto the green
so unlike
yesterday front
nine one under that
and remember the ten is now
being played at just one
hundred
and forty yards
love is short eyed swing
and well
he can't see the result
it's pretty good
quick putt
though coming down the hill that
he's using
he's won fourteen major championships with
oh oh no
no
oh god
oh no
come on now
i mean it was wriggling down the hill
but it just looked like it was going to catch
enough of the lip
it starts down the right
and the accent to me
looks like it
should be turning left that was his best
finish up into his front side
getting through the ball with the driver
we've seen all day on location
we can hit this
just a little bit left of the hole
you'll have a left or right
breaking pot
that's
and here's that precise
right in underneath
it putty built back in nodding sixty five
step
it did catches the left corner tiger woods with a birdie
here at the eleventh walk that one in
maybe a squeeze cut
started left
but i believe this is overcutting
frank
saying that you write about those fields
look for this thing to jump
it's just one eighty
two to the front
i'm just shy twelve
going to work with
let's see if he goes with something a little less lofted
nicely done
nice
make me a formality
angle that whole location
perched over there
it was a nine
and just left of the flag
looks like a little left to right
putney's left himself
and you know all about those
look at this
look at that boy
he looks so good
over those pots at the moment
some weeks
you just
grimace through the ball there
it finds the first kind of rough
sitting
nicely like good that first cut flattered or flight
it's interesting
you would say that year
so you watched him coming off the driving range
talking with pat perez and laughing
and now a couple
other players not
to play the skip rangers flew a little too far the green
the trick is to figure out
which one to use a bumping
around here
it's interesting
he chose to chip that they're putting through it that first caught a rough
a lot of players
would have punted that or belly to wedge
that's sick three wood here for tiger
and it's hanging down the right side
it looks to me
like it
should find fair
so there you go
that's one strategy three
we're just all right
just
slide it down a little dra
the hang up
it's tron
it creeps away
seeing it on
so many different occasions
take his four
however
fifteen and move along three holes to go in the second round
and not miss this screen
right
so cut it towards that right hole
that's what he tried to do
but he's pulled another iron shot
how should i find the ground
okay
that's gonna say that water does lurk on the left side
that's fine though
oh that was a not as best part this week
he's had good pace
mostly
so that was a very slow part
how's his body gonna take it
that's a big question
mark
but this is for a part
yeah
let's try them
a little hole was also getting tough to seek
no problem seeing this run
right down the center of beautiful
about that that was long too
he flew it
three hundred yards
it works on down the slope
that'll leave him
a short approach in here
solid strike working towards
a flag of cut
previous one bounce right back here with a birdie
impressive
it was two beautiful shots we
launched really high
but drifting out to the right towards that first bunker through the fairway
fortunately short of it
just ballooned up to the flag
well struck towards
the center of the green
oh yeah
look at this
be better than a three four
finish
it was flawless that the first round after that sluggish start today
it's just being patient
i think that's the way for eagle at eighteen
power that one by
and that goes in so tiger woods has a two shot
lead through three six holes of his first ever zoo championship
slide this on with that back hole
location
cutting back towards
the flag
let's go steve
that's one thing we're going to hear a lot that here
those are motor drives on
those cameras going away on the show
life into the chasing pack
speed right this
start with center
and it is a dji wonder
doing what you did yesterday
craie's looking out left
yeah
it was stopped in the center of the
flush
it's okay
does start on the center of the green
but it's just not coming
it's gonna be a good shot though
he's been feeling it with the potter all week
roll the ball
it stops for a good line
a little bit lower that is hammered towards
the left side of the green
and the lead is now back to three ready
there's two rounds
stocks left
but it's not cutting
just to get up
but relaxed that's a dangerous combination
at about
well he may have hit the ferry here
filled beautiful
little gentle cut
there was a free swing there
he got all the way through that mall that fabulous
or that they even called their names
and they just went to this different place
you see the look on his face
nineteen cards count backwards to plague
distance control
you can see the line few in the game
we've ever put it at the level and tiger
his bud consider consider the pressure situations chance here to extend his lead
just over right grizero to trouble
this time
it's a narrow
being very comfortable
hitting the car
that's what he's trying to do here
you drifting back on the right
it's ford
give an inch
four yards behind this flag
hey sonic
that's a good six seven feet pass
keeps that blade so rezoned them in a bit
this
for each shot and tiger
second
to just left of the flag
go go go
ready
so i had to draw that one a little bit cut out in front of it out to the right
so you'd like the worst t shots he hits or when he tries to draw it
quite a bit
so they don't
set up with the face
quite a bit open
as if he's gonna lock
this pretty high in the air
let's see what he does
and low
and i was in poor
stripe
sort of stuck the club into the ground
clean strike more
so maybe than he thought
so he's gonna have a good
a fourth easiest toll on the golf course
i got smartly left of the flag
usually in complete control
too much on the high side
we're excited
slow that sort of hobbled
halfway through the parts of
that's like
we had
like a good draw smack
didn't like that
but for sure
another wall struck on this
right of the flag
cozy it down there
but well
short like you
said
frank
that's kind of basically the green
look great they get good
what connors was
that's when drifting right
i believe the speed through the railway
way up
and you're cutting
it's going towards
the other girl
just show
you get back
you hit back
heavy
try the woods
well
let's we're not pulled this cutting back towards
the flames
they're gorgeous
looking shot on
this one not pull this
cutting back towards
the flames
they're gorgeous
looking shot
this morning
this morning trying to take it down the right side of the
i start making the shoulders
mrs starling left and trying to cut
it's something grain high
pinball fight normal trying to cut back
safely towards
the center of the ring
just on the high side one
there's meout by the body was going to hold up in the day
playing
maybe twenty seven
not much movement
again this
thought it was going to change by the time
it didn't change
the tight fit up there
i'm gonna paste in
this was a nine on it
but just drifting away from the black night
let's allow the fans to tell you
whether this birdie putt goes home
by the hit
and this is the fight down the right hand side of the field
he's trying to turn over
sat down and
it's solid
come out
not his best pu
he doesn't want his stri
got it out in front of it
going out to the right
big high cut
speed in that golf swing
beautiful
looking shots started at the center
comes up
just a little
can tee off on the next souls
so this will be it for tonight
well
they can just started
this one did start left
but unfortunately
not cut
missed the railway
oh god
all right kick
oh my goodness
starting toward senators
sam
maybe a miss strike
and in the front
whatever point
it's going to be denied by the ridge
all right
got it
oh r is the first
he's a sonic
so only apart for tiger
good opportunity
squandered their
this starts down and left hand side
shot now for tiger at the fourteen
three
three hundred
and twenty one was watching intently
what messi on was doing up at the green
a beautiful shot
he gets it in that back shelf
he's got a chance for birdie
simply the best fit with the driver
took that bunker out of playground
so
when the fourteen off the tee was good that one in this situation
much higher on a very good line
the left
so the lead remains at three
well there started actually flying and cut it towards the second
pull brown off the path face
bit of a mystery to damage done
we call the last time c
i'm so confident on the team
was a knockdown started at the center of the green
just never cut
got to work to think that's what he had in mind
when he came to the seventeenth
love it
you have to watch
that two shot
right where you'd expect
as we look at the winning putt
and that is there's a
so cool to hear
him
say once again